<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Anna Kurtin</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Anna Kurtin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I Got Into Coding</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/10/coding-demonstration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/10/coding-demonstration/</guid>
      <description>Ah, coding. Love it or hate it, it’s an essential tool in many biologists’ repertoire. Going into college, I had no idea that there would be so much coding and computer work involved. In fact, if you had shown freshman year me one of my latest projects, I would have run in the other direction!
This pretty sums up how I got into coding. Credit: unknown
Throughout high school, I was infamous among my family and friends for being hopelessly lost when working with computers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kinkajou Travels (Costa Rica Internship Blog)</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/09/kinkajou-travels-costa-rica-internship-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/09/kinkajou-travels-costa-rica-internship-blog/</guid>
      <description>In the fall semester of my junior year, I took part in an internship abroad with Kids Saving the Rainforest, a wildlife rescue, sanctuary, and conservation center in Quepos, Costa Rica. This fantastic study abroad experience taught me more than I could have imagined about conservation, animal care, Costa Rican history and culture, research, ecotourism and more. I maintained a blog documenting my experiences there, and while it is by no means comprehensive, it gives a good account of my time in Costa Rica.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
